metacafe.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy on MetaCafe

The use of the Metacafe Web Site(s) and/or Metacafe software and any Metacafe services and products (collectively, the "Web Site") provided by MetaCafe, LLC ("MetaCafe") are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the MetaCafe  Terms & Conditions. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Web Site.

## General

MetaCafe takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEB SITE), YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. MetaCafe reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Web Site following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Web Site, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the Web Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Collection of Information Personal Information. Use of certain features of the Web Site may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nickname (or other user ID) and a password.

### Non personally identifiable Information

MetaCafe may also collect or receive additional non-personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Web Site, and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on the Web Site.

MetaCafe may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the Web Site and pages are visited or when a MetaCafe client is used.

### How is the information being used?

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by MetaCafe, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Web Site; and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. Please note that MetaCafe may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while MetaCafe's business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about Metacafe users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures, as determined by MetaCafe in good faith. Furthermore, MetaCafe may transfer personally identifiable information in the event of a transfer of ownership of MetaCafe or any of its Web Sites or products, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy.

### Cookies

MetaCafe may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Web Site, including to operate and improve offerings through the Web Site; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Web Site; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you. MetaCafe does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Web Site may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. To disable cookies, follow the instructions in your web browser.

### Local Shared Object (Flash Cookie)

We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click here. If you disable Flash cookies, you won't have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. Click here to cancel an existing account.

## Behavioral Targeting

### Third Party Advertising

MetaCafe or its advertisers may use third party ad networks and ad serving companies to help sell and present advertisements online in connection with the Web Site. These third party ad companies may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, compile anonymous statistics about Web Site users, to serve you advertisements tailored to interests youhave shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In so doing, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of these technologies by these third party ad companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not MetaCafe’s and MetaCafe disclaims all liability in connection therewith. These third party ad companies may also monitor the Web Site for the purpose of reporting Web Site traffic, statistics, advertisements, "click-throughs" and/or other activities. MetaCafe works with the following ad networks, whose privacy policies are available on their respective sites: Google, Mog, Tidal.tv, Openx, 24/7 Real Media, Beanstock and Rubicon. You may opt out of having the advertising that you see on our site targetedspecifically to you by clicking on the Privacy Manager or going to the respective sites’ privacy policy(ies) and following the directions. To opt out of Google’s “interest-based ads” and to learn more about Google’s collection of your personal information to serve ads in connection with the Web Site, [click here](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/). You can disable cookies, including those used by ad networks, by following the instructions in your web browser. MetaCafe does not provide advertisers access to any personally identifiable information that you have provided to MetaCafe (keeping in mind that anything you have elected to share publicly on the site is available to everyone to see).

Last updated: April 22, 2013.

### Security

MetaCafe has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personally identifiable information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our personnel that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information, are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information.

### California Privacy Policy

MetaCafe's privacy policy is to share personal information only with the owner's informed consent. With your consent, from time-to-time, MetaCafe may provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know. If you have further inquires regarding MetaCafe's information sharing practices, please let us know at this number: +1 415.882.7069.

### Special Note for Parents

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, MetaCafe does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Web Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Web Site is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Web Site at any time or in any manner. If MetaCafe learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Web Site without verified parental consent, then MetaCafe will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information

**Deletion (Opt-Out).** In order to delete the personally identifiable information you submitted, notify us at support@metacafe.com that you wish to delete your personally identifiable information or any part thereof contained at our databases. **Modification.** If you wish to modify or update your personally identifiable information, use the Web Site or application interface. If you need help, please contact us at support@metacafe.com

Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from MetaCafe's database will not prevent MetaCafe from using gathered anonymous information. **Third Parties' Practices.** This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other providers of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that MetaCafe does not own or control, or does not employ or manage. See also, "Third Party Ad Advertising."

### Non-U.S. Users

The Web Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Web Site from a jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Web Site, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

Last updated: October 3, 2012.

## Submission Rules

### General Guidelines

You want to upload some videos? We love that! After all, uploading short flicks to Web Site is one of the five greatest things you can do in the world. First, there are some rules to follow. We know, you hate rules, but they exist to keep Web Site from devolving into chaos and becoming another business horror story. So here you go (take notes, we'll be testing you later):

  * No cloning allowed. No, we're not talking about producing identical sheep in the lab - that's cool. We're talking about duplicating videos that already exist on the site. We HATE duplicates, because repetition repetition sucks sucks. So before you upload a video to Web Site, please conduct a search to see if it already exists here.
  * Ten is enough. No, we're not talking about that cheesy TV show from the Seventies. We're talking about the length of your video: keep it under 10 minutes. Anything longer than that will be removed automatically by our system.
  * Keep your pants on. We're not prudes here, but we want Web Site to serve as wide a community as possible. This means we will not allow sexually explicit videos on the site. Those are simply 2H4M (Too Hot For Metacafe).
  * What about partial nudity or implied sexuality? We're not afraid of the odd 'wardrobe malfunction' but it's better to practice safe sex and put an 18+ filter on it.
  * Filter that violence. Please remember that Web Site is all about entertainment and entertainment should not come at the expense of others. So if your video contains violence, please stick the appropriate filter on it:
  * 18+: For real-world violence including physical attacks; for injuries, gruesome scenes, or explicit language.
  * MetaCafe will reject videos which portray illegal acts of violence or videos that show or imply human fatalities however newsworthy such footage may seem in context.
  * Dress for success. Package your videos with killer titles, descriptions, thumbnails, and tags to attract viewers. But, please, be accurate, or we'll tell all the people you deceived exactly where you sleep.
  * Irresistible Titles: What's in a name? Everything. Boring titles = no views, so give your video a title no one can resist.
  * Teaser Descriptions: Don't you hate it when someone tells you the surprise ending of a movie before you've seen it? ("Dude, did you hear that Darth Vader is Luke's dad?") So go ahead and describe the contents of your video in vivid detail, but don't give away the punch line.
  * Eye-Catching Thumbnails: Pick an image from your video that accurately represents its contents and grabs attention. But if it's something gross, don't show it - we like to eat while browsing the site.
  * Tag Away: Use as many tags as you want to describe your video. That helps people find it in a search.
  * Pick a channel. If your video fits more than one channel, choose one that applies most. Still can't decide? Take a coin, assign one channel to heads, one channel to tails, then flip it. Later, see a counselor about how you let coins shape your life.

Last updated: October 3, 2012

## Metacafe House Rules

We built Metacafe to be a creative community buzzing with energy. (We love a great buzz.) So we've established a few house rules to keep it going:

  * Helpful Criticism: Want better videos? Then provide suggestions instead of smack! Good advice goes a long way in building a better Web Site. And if you think you can do better, don't just say it - SHOW IT with your own video.
  * Save The Creativity For The Videos: Don't try to sneak onto top lists by manipulating the results. For example, posting lots of comments on your own video to get onto the "Most Discussed" list won't get you anywhere. (We've got trained dogs to sniff out cheats.)
  * Keep It Clean: There are 1,000,000 words in the English language alone, including some cool ones like "nubile," "psychedelic," and "obfuscation." Flaunt your language skills here, and leave the profanity and other garbage talk at home.
  * No Haters: Our community has zero tolerance for intolerance, so no defamatory, racist, sexist or homophobic talk. This includes threats of violence or sexual assault against other site users or people appearing in videos. Offenders will be banned forever from Web Site.

We hate playing cops - it takes time away from watching videos and building a killer site - so we hope this little statement does the job of keeping the Metacafe buzz going and growing.

Last updated: October 3, 2012
